欢迎回来
约翰尼·德普诉前妻 安柏·赫德的诽谤案
Welcome back. Johnny Depp's defamation trial
在电视上和社交媒体上同步直播
is playing out in real time on television and on social media,
（2022年4月 弗吉尼亚）
有数以百万记的人 在爆出惊人的细节 并且站边
where millions are poring over shocking details and taking sides.
（抖音）
安柏 你感觉如何？
Amber, how you feeling?
我关于这集节目的视频 有将近50万播放量
My video about this pod episode is at almost 500,000 views,
而那期视频是我昨天才发布的
and I just posted it yesterday.
我们必须看到很多方面
It has many facets that we have to look at,
包括名声 “我也是”运动 取消文化
including fame, the Me Too movement, cancel culture.
这简直就是一场完美风暴
It is just a, uh... sort of a perfect storm, if you will.
超过埃隆·马斯克成为第一名
Number one over Elon Musk.
是乔·拜登的四倍以上
More than four times Joe Biden.
是堕胎意见的五倍以上
Abortion opinion, more than five times greater.
是乌克兰战争的六倍以上
The Ukraine war, more than six times greater.
这是全国互联网上最热门的事件
This story is the biggest story online in the nation.
（在审判期间 有超过200小时的实况报道）
（数以百万计的人 收看、评论和分享）
新闻主播在法院外排起了长队
News anchors lined up outside the courthouse.
法庭里有很多摄像头 每分钟都在直播
Numerous cameras inside the courtroom live-streaming every minute.
带我们去参观一下 可以给我们的移动设备拍个视频
Uh, take us for a little tour of our... I think we have video of our mobile setup.
我们这里有时会有供暖和空调
We actually have heating and air conditioning sometimes in here.
大家在推特直播 在视频直播
People are live-tweeting, people are live-streaming.
这都是什么意思？最后如何收场？
What does it all mean? Where does it end?
这成为了社交媒体马戏团
It's been, uh, you know, a social media circus
充斥着来自 创作者、网红和普通人的评论
of commentary from creators and influencers and, uh... and laypeople.
我觉得这件事的真正意义 早就被社交媒体遗忘了
I think that the truth was lost on social media, uh, quite some time ago.
大家对抖音上 传播的错误信息有了新的担忧
Well, there are new concerns about the spread of misinformation on TikTok.
研究人员调查显示
According to researchers,
美国用户在抖音上 花费的时间比在推特上长三倍
American users spend three times as much time on TikTok than on Twitter.
再多给我们解释一下 这个应用程序的设计和它的麻烦之处
Explain for us more about the app's design and why it is particularly problematic.
这是一个短视频平台
You have a platform that uses short videos.
它有一个非常强大而神秘的推荐算法
It has a powerful and very mysterious recommendation algorithm.
它有十亿用户
You've got a billion users
不断地快速筛选视频
that are constantly filtering through a very fast-moving feed.
视频可以很轻易地被操控和重新发布
Videos can be very easily manipulated and republished.
我走出卧室时 一巴掌打在我脸上
I was walking out of the bedroom, slapped me across the face,
我说：“约翰尼 你打我”
and I said, "Johnny, you hit me."
你打我
You just hit me. Hit me.
有一些模仿视频会被很多人当真
There are parody videos that often get mistaken as fact.
我们当时并肩坐着
人们都痴迷于这个案件
People are obsessed with this case. On TikTok,
人们可以在抖音上广播他们的理论
people could really broadcast their theories.
我当时坐在地毯上
I was sitting there on this carpet.
尤其是这个案件被直播 你可以拿到全程录像
Especially when the case is live in court and you have all this footage.
你可以给他们看到真实发生的事情 大家在发什么？
You could show them authentically what is going on. What are people posting?
聊聊澳大利亚
...talked about Australia.
我认为这可能会决定这个案件
I think this might decide the case,
因为这是双方争论最激烈的矛盾焦点
because this is where the parties are alleging the most significant dispute,
而且他们的说法完全相反
and they're in such contradiction,
陪审团只能认同其中一个的真实性
that the jury can only think one of them is true.
我认为他们会得出结论 其中一方
I think they're going to come to the conclusion
在澳大利亚的事情上撒了谎
that one of them is lying about Australia.
让我们来看看他们描述的事情经过
Let's take a look about what they said happened.
我当时在参与 《加勒比海盗5》的拍摄
I was... I was working on Pirates of the Caribbean five.
德普先生 当时赫德小姐 和你一起在澳大利亚吗？
Mr. Depp, was Ms. Heard in Australia with you?
她后来过来了 是的
She came a little later, yes.
赫德小姐去澳大利亚 找你的时候 发生了什么事？
And what happened when Ms. Heard came to visit you in Australia?
《德普 vs 赫德： 好莱坞夫妻诽谤案》
剧名：《第二集：全网关注》
谢谢 约翰尼·德普来了
Thank you very much. Johnny Depp's here.
我听说过这件事 现在终于看到了 你有一枚订婚戒指
I haven't seen it, but I know it ahead of time, and now I see it,that you're wea... wearing a, uh... a... you have an engagement ring.
（2014年4月 《大卫·莱特曼深夜秀》）
-是的 我戴了一枚女性订婚戒指 -对 但你要结婚了吧
- I do, I have a female engagement ring... - Yeah. - ...on my finger. - But you... you, uh, uh, you're getting married.
是啊
- Well, it's... uh, yeah. Uh, yeah. - Yeah.
对 但男人戴订婚戒指 这不是很常见 对吧？
But it's... it's not typical for a m-man to wear an engagement ring, is it?
不常见
No.
但我的女孩戴嫌大了 所以…
It was too big for my girl, so, uh...
你的结婚对象…对了 她也上过节目
So the woman you're, uh... Who's been on the show, by the way.
-安柏 是的 -很棒
- Amber, yeah. Yeah. - Oh, lovely.
安柏！
Amber!
安柏 向左看！
Amber, look to your left!
安柏 笑一个 安柏！
Amber. Big smile, Amber!
我几年前就向赫德小姐求婚了
I had proposed to Ms. Heard a couple of years before, I believe,
我们偶尔会聊一聊 什么时候适合抽出时间
so we talked occasionally about when would be the right time between schedules
来举办婚礼和度蜜月
so that we could actually have a wedding and a honeymoon,
然后去澳大利亚工作
and... and then go on to do the work in Australia.
我要和我的一生挚爱结婚
I was marrying the love of my life.
这很复杂
It was complicated,
但他曾是我的一生挚爱
but he was the love of my life.
女士们 先生们 约翰尼·德普
Ladies and gentlemen, Johnny Depp!
我们是为了…
We all left for the island for the...
梦想中的婚礼上岛的 大概吧
well, the dream wedding, I guess.
我们走过沙滩步道
We walked down the beach aisle,
说了我们的誓言 在祭坛上
said our vows,
对狗仔队竖了中指
and shot the bird, meaning the middle finger, up at the paparazzi while we were on the altar.
然后我们跳舞和庆祝
And we danced and celebrated.
然后我离开了岛屿 因为我得去工作
And then I left the island 'cause I had to go work.
安柏！请看前面
Amber! Straight ahead please.
安柏·赫德比他年轻20岁
Amber Heard is 20 years younger
她在好莱坞建立了 自己的事业和知名度
and was building a career and name recognition within Hollywood,
但她还远不是 约翰尼·德普那样的明星
but she was certainly nowhere near the star that Johnny Depp was.
-我们跟安柏·赫德在一起 -你好
- Hi, we're here with Amber Heard. - Hi.
介绍一下你的角色
Explain quickly your character.
我扮演的是一个年轻女孩
I play a young girl who's caught up
（圣丹斯电影节 2009年）
陷入了洛杉矶1980年代 快节奏且贪图享乐的生活方式
in the fast-paced, decadent, 1980s lifestyle of Los Angeles,
她是一个美丽的女人 最终…
She's a beautiful woman who ultimately, um...
最终 这种美丽 导致了她和其他人物的灭亡
Ultimately, that beauty causes her demise and the demise of other characters around her.
那是一个很有趣的角色
And it was an interesting part.
我在洛杉矶搭乘公交车 那是在智能手机时代之前
I took the bus around L.A. It was before smartphones.
我拿着托马斯街道地图和换洗的背心
I had a... a Thomas Guide and a change of tank tops,
非常努力地跑试镜
and I just hustled from one audition to the other.
-这里 安柏 -安柏 这里
- Right here, Amber. - Amber, right here.
那之后的进展很缓慢
It's been a slow progression, I guess, since then,
我要么是在大片里出演非常小的角色
you know, of doing either tiny bit parts in bigger movies
要么是在没人去看的电影里 出演重要一点的角色
or doing larger roles in movies that no one would see,
其实现在也差不多是那样
and I guess, you know, it still is kind of like that.
离开岛上之后 你就必须去工作
When you say you left the island, you had to go to work,
你当时在做什么？
what... what were you working on?
（《丹麦女孩》）
我当时在伦敦拍《丹麦女孩》
I was filming The Danish Girl in London.
我当时在为那部电影做准备工作
I was there doing, kind of, prep work for that film.
我要去往澳大利亚
I was going off to Australia.
先生们！
Gentlemen!
当时的计划就是我拍完电影之后
The plan was always for me to wrap on my movie
就去澳大利亚找他 他在那里拍摄《加勒比海盗5》
and then come and join him in Australia where he was filming Pirates five.
好 那大概是什么时候？
Okay, and when approximately was that?
那是3月3日
That was March 3rd.
各位 我非常震惊于你们对这个频道
Guys, I am shocked at the massive amounts of love and support
展现出的那么多爱与支持
that you guys have been showing this channel,
尤其是我们关于 为约翰尼·德普讨公道运动的报道
and specifically our coverage of the Justice for Johnny Depp movement.
欢迎回来本期的达斯新闻特别编
Welcome back to another episode of Darthn3ws special edition,
“大家都爱约翰尼”
"Everybody Loves Johnny."
不对 划掉这句 “大家都讨厌安柏”
Actually, scratch that. "Everybody Hates Amber."
YouTube上有一些创作者
You have creators on platforms like YouTube.
突然之间
All of a sudden,
他们就开始发布关于这场庭审的视频
they're pumping out videos about this trial.
如果你还没有的话 帮个忙？
If you haven't, do me a favor,
点击关注按钮 按下提醒铃
hit the subscribe button, hit the bell for alerts.
大家都在等着看证据 我也是…
I think everybody's waiting to see the evidence. That's what I...
（痞子杰 痞子杰秀音频）
提示一下不知道的人 醒目留言是在YouTube上
For those of you who don't know, Super Chats is a way, on YouTube,
观众看直播时的打赏手段
for people watching someone streaming to donate.
洛 谢谢你打赏的100
Loww, thank you for the 100 gift, giving me subs. I appreciate that.
我很感激 非常谢谢你
Thank you so much. Thank you, thank you.
它可以让你的评论被置顶 打赏人的名字和额度会被高亮
It allows their comment to go to the top. It kinda highlights that... that person and their donation.
嘿 如果我们还没见过 我是艾米丽·D·贝克 超牛的律师
Hey, there. If we haven't met yet, I'm Emily D. Baker, the badass lawyer,
也是大家最喜欢的法律评论员
and everyone's favorite legal commentator.
我分析新闻和流行文化故事 背后的法律细节
I break down the legal shit behind the news and pop culture stories
这是我们都感兴趣的内容
we all wanna talk about.
我们是来分析 约翰尼·德普诉安柏·赫德案的
We are here to call to order...the case of Johnny Depp v. Amber Heard.
今天 我们要看看现场直播证词
Today, we are watching through live testimony
了解在澳大利亚发生的事情
of what happened in Australia.
（2015年3月 澳大利亚 黄金海岸）
现在 我要请你告知陪审团
Now, I'm going to ask you to take this jury
你到达澳大利亚之后发生的事情
through what happened once you arrived there.
我坐飞机过去 提前到了
Um, I flew in. I arrived early.
我立刻走进了卧室
Uh, I... Immediately, I walked into the bedroom.
我很期待见到他
I was so excited to... to see him.
我期待着开始…我们风格的居家约会
I was looking forward to having this, kind of, you know, "our style" at-home date.
我们是新婚夫妇
You know, a new... we're a new married couple.
我们在结婚之后
We hadn't seen each other
有近一个月没见
for basically a month......after getting married.
我开始吃晚餐 很高兴见到他
And I start dinner and am happy to see him,
那天晚上早些时候
and some point early in that evening,
他拿出一袋摇头丸
he pulls out a bag of MDMA.
我问他那是什么
I asked him what it was,
他告诉我是摇头丸
and he told me it was MDMA.
我很惊讶 因为当时他已经戒毒戒酒了
And I was surprised because, at the time, he had already gotten clean and sober.
是为了婚礼
It was for the wedding.
所以我很惊讶他会掏出这袋药丸
So I was surprised that he would even pull out this bag,
他好像在建议我们一起嗑药
and he kinda seemed to suggest that we should do it together,
我的反应是：“坚决不行
and I was like, "Absolutely not."
我刚刚到这里
Like, "I just got here. I just got here!"
我想见你 想跟你共度时光”
"I wanna see you, I wanna spend time with you."
赫德小姐很难过是因为
Ms. Heard was upset because,
已经来不及写婚前协议了
as it was too late for a pre-nup agreement,
而是在商讨婚后协议
there... there was, uh, discussion of post-nup agreement.
她无法释怀 认为我想订立这份婚后协议
She could not let go of the fact that I was in on this, uh, post-nup agreement
并且我试图欺骗她
and that I was trying to trick her
如果发生什么事
into, uh, essentially getting nothing
她基本上什么都得不到
if, uh...if something were to happen.
她告诉我：“你不相信我”
She's telling me, "You don't trust me, you don't trust me, you don't trust me."
我当时只能试着让她冷静下来
And, um, all I could do was... try to calm her down.
成功了吗？
- That... - Did that work?
没有成功
It did not work, no.
而是升级了 局面变得很疯狂
It escalated and escalated, and t-turned into, uh...madness,
混乱
chaos.
-你能不能… -暴力
- Can you please... - Violence.
你能不能描述一下当时的混乱和暴力
Can you please describe that chaos and violence?
你的本性和身份
你坑害我的方式
让我感到恶心
对我自己！
你那周日为什么会在家里？
Why were you at the house that Sunday?
我被德普的一个助手叫去了他家
I was called to the house by one of Mr. Depp's assistants.
你进屋时有没有观察到什么？
And did you observe anything when you went into the house?
是的 我听到了非常歇斯底里的抽泣
Yeah, I mean, initially, I heard pretty hysterical sobbing,
哭喊
crying,
听起来像是赫德小姐的声音
which sounded like Ms. Heard to me.
就是失控地哭泣 我觉得这么说很合理
Just crying uncontrollably, I think it's fair to say.
楼梯下面有损坏
There was a bit of damage down the steps.
大理石阶梯上有一大块掉了下来
A big chunk had been taken out of the marble staircase.
走到吧台 我能看到损坏
Walking down into the bar, I could see the damage,
一个损坏的乒乓球桌倒在了地板上
a broken ping-pong table, sort of collapsed onto the floor,
吧台那边散落着大量玻璃和罐子
lots of glass and cans strewn around the bar area.
显然浩克来过
Apparently, Hulk came through.
碎玻璃 他也是这么说的
Broken glass is consistent with his version.
你到的时候 都有谁在场？
Who was there when you arrived?
黛比罗伊德在那里
Um, Debbie Lloyd was there.
11点30分 你写了
Eleven-thirty, you wrote,
“医学博士收到客户的短信
"MD received a text message from client
他与妻子争吵 割伤了手指
that he'd been arguing with wife and that he had cut his finger."
病人说
"According to patient,
他的助理和保安正在去接他”
his assistant and security were on their way to pick him up."
你写的？
You wrote that?
根据我的记录 没错
According to my notes, yes.
大卫·基普在场
David Kipper was there.
我进去是为了指示
I went in to instruct
跟着他的人去找到指尖
one of the people with him to look for the tip of the finger,
希望我们能把它接回去
hoping that we would be able to put it back.
范围很广 碎玻璃 血迹
It was pretty extensive, all that broken glass, the blood.
地板上滴了很多血
There were a lot of blood drips across that floor.
地板是奶油色的
It's a kind of cream-colored tiled floor. On the next floor, on the main floor,
在主楼 有一间起居室 里面有一张乳白色的沙发
there's a sitting room with a couch on... a cream-colored couch,
垫子上有相当大量的血迹
which had a fair amount of blood drips on the cushions,
我们设置了一个艺术工作室 所以有很多从那儿拿的艺术材料
and we'd set up an art studio, so a lot of the art materials from that,
画笔 颜料 地板上有很多颜料
you know, paintbrushes, paint, a lot of paint on the floor.
进入主卧
Going into the master bathroom,
那里有双人水槽和镜子 很大的镜子
there was a his-and-hers sinks and a mirror, a large mirror,
每个水槽上都有 上面写了字
above each of the sinks that had writing on each of them.
我记得每间卧室的被套上都有血迹
Both of the bedrooms, I think, had blood on the duvet covers.
就是这样
That's about the extent of it.
哦 就是这些？
Oh, is that all?
这些该谁清理？
Uh, whose job was it to clean all that up?
该我
It was mine. It was mine.
我就直说吧
Well, I'll... I'll just cut to the chase.
我记得 那天我最后把自己锁在
I... I think that I ended up locking myself
至少九间卧室和洗手间里
in about, at lea... at least nine bedrooms, bathrooms that day,
因为她敲打着门 喊着污言秽语
um, as she was banging on the doors and screaming obscenities
想要发生肢体冲突
and wanting to, uh, have a physical altercation.
所以你的手指受伤是怎么回事？
So how did it come to be that your finger became injured?
我离开了那里
I left the... place,
就是我躲的那间房
the... the room that I was hiding in,
不叫躲 把自己锁在里面
or not hiding, locked myself into.
然后我下了楼
And I went downstairs,
那里有个吧台
and there was a, uh, bar,
所以我拿了一瓶那里的伏特加
so I grabbed a bottle of vodka that was there,
和一个小酒杯
and a shot glass,
然后坐在吧台
and sat at the bar.
她当时不在附近
She was nowhere around.
我给自己倒了两三杯纯伏特加
Poured myself two or three stiff shots of, uh... of the vodka,
那是我很久以来第一次喝酒
first taste of alcohol I'd had in a long time.
然后她来到吧台 看到我在那儿
then she came down to the bar and found me there,
果然就开始大喊：“你又喝酒了”
and of course started screaming, "Oh, you're drinking again!"
“怪物”之类的
"Ah, the monster," and all that. Um...
你可以看到他的感受
You can see how he feels about that.
他拿着一瓶酒
Um, he holds up this bottle,
然后用瓶子指着我
and kind of gesturing with the... the bottle towards me,
我伸手去拿
and, uh, I reach for it,
他收回了瓶子 嘲笑了一下我
and he'd revoke it, kind of laugh at me.
而且他还拿着瓶子
And he's holding out the bottle.
好像是第三次左右 我拿到了瓶子
I think, maybe the third time or so, I get a hold of it.
我把它拿过来 摔到地上
I pick it up and I slam it down on the ground,
摔在我们中间
right in between us,
我把瓶子砸在地上
and I smashed the bottle on the floor,
把他气坏了
and that really set him off.
她拿起那瓶伏特加
She grabbed the... the bottle of vodka...
然后往后退 然后把它扔到我身上
and then just, uh, kind of stood back and then...hurled it at me.
又拿了第二瓶 更大的一瓶
Takes the second bottle, which was the larger one,
她把大瓶子扔了过来
she threw the large bottle,
摔到了地面
and it made contact
然后碎得到处都是
and shattered, uh, everywhere,
然后我发现我的手指尖
and then I realized that the... the tip of my finger, uh,
被切断了
had been severed.
这是什么照片 德普先生？
What is this a picture of, Mr. Depp?
（法庭证据）
我的手指残肢
The remains of my finger.
我真的不记得 有没有朝他的方向扔东西
I-I-I honestly don't remember if I, um, threw anything in his direction.
我不觉得我扔过
I... I don't think I did.
我只记得他抓住我的睡袍
Um, I just remember him having me by the nightgown.
我记得他甩我 把我扔来扔去 我被他摔打
Um, I remember him flailing me, uh, throwing me around. I'm flailing, um...
某个时刻 他逗弄我 嘲笑我
I remember at one point, he's teasing me, he... taunting me,
他手握我的胸部
that I... he has my, um... my breast in his hand.
我的睡袍完全被脱掉了
Um, my nightgown came completely off.
睡袍被从我身上撕下来了
It was ripped off of me.
所以我完全赤裸
So... I was naked,
我在一块地砖上滑倒
and I'm slipping around on this tile,
在某个时刻
and...at...at some point,
他压在我身上
he's on top of... of... of... of me.
我在台面上
I'm on the countertop,
他抓住了我的脖子
he had me by the neck,
我看着他的眼睛
and I'm looking at h... in his eyes.
我都认不出他了
And I don't see him anymore.
I don't see him anymore.
那不是他 而是漆黑一片
It wasn't him. It was black.
我这辈子从没那么害怕过
I've never been... so scared in my life.
漆黑一片 我看不到他
It was... It was black. I couldn't see him.
我的头被往后撞在吧台上
And... ...my head was bashing against the back of the bar,
我无法呼吸
and I couldn't breathe.
我记得我想爬起来 我滑倒在玻璃上
And I remember trying to get up, and I was slipping on the glass.
我的手和脚都滑了
My feet were slipping, my arms were slipping on the countertop.
我记得我试图爬起来呼吸
And I remember just trying to get up so I could breathe,
这样我就能告诉他 他真的弄疼了我
so I could tell him that he was really hurting me.
我以为他不知道自己在做什么
I didn't think he knew what he was doing.
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know how.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我无法呼吸
I couldn't breathe.
拜托
Please.
我不…
I don't...
我不想这么做
I don't wanna do this.
（安柏·赫德在法庭上 作证称约翰尼·德普）
（用一个玻璃瓶对她实行性侵）
（这是美国第一次完整展现）
（受害者声称自己 遭受性侵的庭审录像）
安柏·赫德在证人席上说
Amber Heard has said on the stand
她无法清晰回忆起事情的发展
she doesn't have a clear recollection of how things unfolded,
但她声称他用一个瓶子性侵了她
but she has alleged that he sexually assaulted her with a bottle.
庭审中有一些东西
There were a couple of points in the trial that,
是本不应该被这样公开的
uh, should have never come out so publicly.
很难评估双方的可信度 原因非常简单
It is so hard to assess the credibility of either Johnny Depp or Amber Heard for one simple reason,
他们都是演员
they're both actors.
他们很擅长 让人们感受到他们想要的感觉
They're good at getting people to feel the way that they want them to feel.
（很多社交媒体评论员 都对安柏·赫德的证词）
（充满怀疑和批判）
（为约翰尼讨公道）
欢迎来到爆米花星球 我是安迪·西诺尔 我不会撒谎
Welcome to Popcorned Planet, I'm Andy Signore, and I'm not gonna lie,
今天很艰难
today was rough.
我为外面的幸存者感到难过
I'm feeling bad for all the survivors out there
他们刚看到那场表演 因为我完全不相信
that just watched this performance 'cause I'm not buying it,
我收到了很多信息
and I've gotten so many messages from so many of you
你们中的很多人都有相似的经历
who have been through similar experiences,
而且你们也并不相信
and you're not buying it either.
他压在我身上 我看着他的眼睛
Like, he was on top of me, and I'm loo... I... I'm looking at h... in his eyes,
我都认不出他了
and I don't see him anymore.
I don't see him anymore.
捆扎痕迹和指痕的淤青都非常常见
Ligature marks and finger marks bruising is very, very common.
我很抱歉你们有那样的经历
And I'm sorry that that was your experience,
但感谢你们在聊天区分享这段经历
but thank you for sharing your experience with the chat.
所以他们说： “这些是我们觉得困惑的东西”
So they're like, "Look, these are the things we find, uh, confusing."
“安柏·赫德精神变态” 现在是推特的热门话题 所以…
"Amber Heard is a psychopath" is currently trending on Twitter, so, uh...
（安柏·赫德是个骗子）
如果你在精神和身体上受到虐待
If you are mentally and physically abused,
一个家庭暴力的人
like, a person of domestic violence,
男性或女性
male or female,
你能否上法庭
would you be able to go to court,
走上证人席
get on the stand,
并成为一个乳臭未干 自以为是的婊子？
and be a lairy, smarmy bitch?
有人看过《消失的爱人》吗？
Has anyone seen Gone Girl?
等待你一无所知的丈夫 开始一天的生活
Wait for your clueless husband to start his day.
精心布置你的犯罪现场
Meticulously stage your crime scene.
是假的 太假了
It's fake. It is so fake!
她怎么能够那样
Like, how could you make such a mockery
对受害者进行嘲讽？
of the victims like she's doing?
用物体进行性侵是非常严重的
Sexual penetration with an object is really severe,
而且跟她对约翰尼·德普的 其他描述不相符
and unlike the rest of what she says about Johnny Depp,
这需要施暴者有施虐狂倾向
almost requires some sort of sadistic nature,
所以我觉得澳大利亚事件 他的版本更加可信
so I think Australia, his story's more believable.
这不只是新闻报道或诉讼 而是已经变成了一场文化运动
This has moved away from, like, a news story or a lawsuit,
（德拉拉·格尔吉安 创作者 维尔档案播客嘉宾）
and it's... it's... it's transformed into a cultural moment.
以我的年龄 还没经历过 OJ辛普森审判的影响
And I wasn't old enough to experience the impact of the O.J. Simpson trial,
但如果让我猜的话
but if I had to guess,
这场官司对全世界的影响
the hold, the chokehold that this lawsuit has on the world...
-应该有那么高 -…可以相提并论
- It's up there, yeah. - ...it's comparable.
以及今天信息和新闻的传播方式
And also the ways in which information and news are spread
跟从前完全不一样
is very different today than it was before.
OJ如果有抖音…
O.J. TikTok would have been...
-天啊 -…太疯狂了
- Oh, my God. - ...wild.
非常疯狂
Truly wild.
-非常疯狂 -是的
- Truly wild. - Yeah.
（在抖音上）
（用户们可以自己编辑庭审视频）
（反响非常巨大）
社交媒体 显然在这个案子中起了作用
Social media is clearly playing a role in this case.
我不能告诉你 我在社交媒体上花了多少时间
I cannot tell you how much time I spend dealing with folks on social media.
但我告诉你 约翰尼·德普的粉丝非常狂热
And I tell you what, the Johnny Depp folks are fanatics.
在为TMZ工作时
And while working for TMZ,
你有没有参与到 与赫德小姐相关的任务中？
were you involved in any assignments related to Ms. Heard?
有的
I was.
12号 我们收到了一段视频
On the 12th, we received a video,
是赫德小姐拍摄的 约翰尼·德普猛击一些柜子的画面
um, depicting, um, Johnny Depp, um, s-slamming some cabinets that was captured by Ms. Heard.
这次审判中播放的视频
How does that video that was played in this trial
跟你2016年8月12日 收到的视频有何区别？
compare to the one you received on August 12, 2016?
庭审中播放的视频
It was much shorter than the video we had recei...
比我们收到的视频短很多
uh, than the video that's been played in this trial.
这里播放的视频开头
There was some... a bit at the beginning that was played here,
有赫德小姐放置好相机
which Ms. Heard is, um, seemingly, sort of, setting up the camera
然后就位的画面
and getting into position,
最后还有一点
and then there's a bit at the end
是她好像在偷偷观望摄像头
where she's seemingly sniggering and looks at the camera.
那部分不在我们收到的视频里
That part was not present in what we received.
TMZ剪辑了视频吗？
Did TMZ edit the video?
-一点都没有 -没有问题了
- No, not even a little. - - Nothing further, Your Honor.
交叉盘问？
Cross-examination?
是的
Yes.
所以你知道这个案子 正在被转播 对吧？
Uh, so, you know this case is being televised, right?
我知道有摄像头
I... I am aware that there are cameras.
所以这让你有15分钟的名气
And so this gets you your 15 minutes of fame.
-反对 法官大人 争论性问题 -我可以问这个问题
Objection, Your Honor. Argumentative. I... I can ask that question.
反对无效
Overruled.
所以我不会从中得到任何好处
我这么做其实会成为TMZ的靶子
那是一个非常爱打官司的公司
我不是在追求15分钟的名声
...and I'm not seeking any 15 minutes here.
虽然你可以推测
Though you may... you're welcome to speculate.
我可以对你有同样的推测 你让赫德成为你的客户
I could say the same thing, by taking Amber Heard as a client, for you.
当你走上法庭 必须作证 而有证据被提出
The issue when you go in court and when you have to testify and when there's evidence brought,
（伊丽莎白·瓦格迈斯特 《视相》首席记者）
（维尔档案播客嘉宾）
这就是为什么名人要和解 以避免公开他们的脏事
That's why celebrities always settle cases. You never want to go into court for that very reason.
难道他们不能私下解决吗？
Could they not have figured this out privately? Um...
我们之前在节目上讨论过这个
I think... And we've talked about this before on the show.
我认为让公众知道也是一种策略
I think that making it, um, accessible to the public was a strategy,
可能是约翰尼的团队提出的
I think, probably brought to the table by Johnny's team.
这个播客只为娱乐
This podcast is for entertainment purposes only.
这次德普和赫德的庭审 大家的参与度非常高
With this Depp/Heard trial, the engagement is phenomenal.
看到大家都参与进来真是太酷了
I mean, it's just so cool to see everyone get involved
大家想知道法律程序和相关法律
and wanna know about the legal process and the laws that are involved.
但正义的问题在于它与真相无关
But that's... The thing is about justice is that it's not about the truth,
与对错无关
it's not about right or wrong.
不幸的是
Unfortunately,
它事关法官或陪审团相信什么
it's about what the judge or jury believes,
这取决于提出什么信息
and that's...and on the information that's presented.
所以庭审就是剧场
And that's why trials are theater.
这本该是对真相的探寻
It's not nec... It's supposed to be this search for the truth,
但事实上是我们在导演 我们应该带来怎样的证人
but it's really about us orchestrating what witnesses we're gonna bring in,
我们要讲述这个故事 应该怎样规划证据
the order of proof that we're gonna present this story,
我们要怎么讲述
and how we're gonna do it,
我们要保留什么 规避什么
what we're gonna keep in, what we're gonna keep out.
这里是《被扰乱的法律》
This is Law Disrupted,
今天我们有幸 与卡米尔·巴斯克斯对话
and today we have the privilege of speaking with Camille Vasquez.
约翰尼的证词是我们的关键点
Johnny's testimony was a... a key point for us.
那是全世界和本案陪审团第一次
It was the first time that the world, really the jury, right, in... in this case,
听到他用自己的语言进行描述
the jury got to hear from him in his own words.
我们要给他机会开口说真话
We needed to give him the opportunity to speak and speak freely.
我们向陪审团介绍了约翰尼·德普 以及真正的约翰尼·德普是谁
We introduced the jury to Johnny Depp and who the real Johnny Depp was.
所以我们向陪审团介绍他的妹妹
So, we introduced the jury to his sister,
她能够提供背景
who was able to give a background
介绍那个小男孩 在成为约翰尼·德普之前是什么样
about who the little boy was... ...before he became Johnny Depp,
以及这个男人现在是什么样
and who the man is now.
谢谢 女士们 先生们 好了 你的第一个证人
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. All right, your first witness.
邓布罗斯基小姐 你能告诉陪审团
Miss Dembrowski, would you please tell the jurors
在你的成长过程中
what your relationship with Johnny was like
和约翰尼的关系如何吗？
when you were growing up?
约翰尼和我关系很好
Johnny and I were very close. Uh...
我们就是朋友 我们像是最好的朋友
We were just friends. We were like best friends.
邓布罗斯基小姐
Miss Dembrowski,
你和你双亲的关系如何？
how would you describe your parents' relationship?
很复杂
That was complicated.
我的童年…
Um, I had a very...
非常有趣
...interesting childhood,
直到一定年纪前 我都以为我的童年很普通
um, one that I thought was normal until a certain age.
你能告诉他们你吸毒的历史吗？
Could you please tell them about your history of substance use?
大概在四五岁的时候
At about the age of, I don't know,
我也说不好了
f-four, five years old,
我很清楚地记得我妈妈
I... I can remember vividly my... my mom
叫我从她挂在门后的包里
telling me to go get her nerve pills, you know, um,
去拿她的神经药
out of her purse that was hanging on the back of the door.
所以我会去拿神经药
So I'd go get the nerve pills and I'd take it,
几年后
and, um, you know, after a few years,
我开始注意到…
you start to notice...
我开始想“神经药”
well, you start to think about "nerve pills."
“神经药”
"Nerve pill."
她吃了那些“神经药”之后 似乎会平静下来
And then she seemed to calm down after she took those "nerve pills."
所以当我11岁的时候…
So, when I was 11 years old,
我想冷静下来
I wanted to calm down.
我会帮我妈妈拿她的神经药
I'd bring my mom her nerve pill,
我会走开
I would walk away...
然后我自己也吃一颗
...and I would take one myself,
用来逃避我们当时
to escape the... the chaotic... nature
非常混乱的生活
of... of what w... of what we were living, uh, through.
我的妈妈
My mother was...
非常难以预测
quite unpredictable,
而且她非常暴力
and she was quite violent,
还有身体上的痛苦
and the physical pain,
我们学会应对 学会接受
y-you learn to deal with, you learn to accept it,
但心理和情感上的虐待
but the, uh, psychological and emotional abuse,
我觉得会把我们撕成碎片
that's what, uh...that's what kind of tore us up, I think.
德普先生 你有没有过药物上瘾？
Mr. Depp, is there any substance you've ever been addicted to?
-有 -是什么药物？
- Yes. - And... And what is that?
洛西考酮
Roxicodone.
目前为止 大家都在用自己读到的东西
So far, everybody's just making these speculations
进行推测
based off of whatever they're reading.
我们在此之前 都没有听过当事人的陈述
We haven't heard it out of the horse's mouth until now.
现在我们听到了 或者开始听到这些事情
And now that we have, or started to hear about these things...
这只会让他看起来 是一个更加真诚的人
it only makes him seem like a more honest human being,
更加讨喜的人
a more likable person.
我上瘾的药物
The pills that I was addicted to, the...
洛西考酮
the Roxicodone,
是非常强大的阿片类药物
which are very, very powerful opiates,
两颗就能让我失去意识
two of those would knock me out.
你会开始所谓的“点头”
You go on what's called "the nod,"
然后它会让你立即沉睡
and then it takes you away into sleep.
是非常深的睡眠
It's just very deep sleep.
我们看到约翰尼·德普 对自己的药物滥用史非常坦诚
We see Johnny Depp very open about his drug use,
我认为另一方会试图用这一点扳倒他
that I think the other side was going to try to use against him,
但他知道 他会承认 他的朋友也承认
but he knew, he's going to admit to it, his friends admitted to it,
他们让对方的攻击不那么有杀伤力
and they kind of, you know, took the sting out of it from the other side.
没什么严重后果了
They... Nothing really happened with it anymore, right?
一旦你承认了 他们就做不了什么
Once you admit it, they can't really do anything with it.
无法采取行动
There's no movement.
这是一张你在 黑色皮沙发上昏倒的照片 是么？
This is a picture of you on a... on a black leather couch, passed out, correct?
昏倒是一种有趣的说法
Passed out's an interesting way of putting it.
也许是睡着
Maybe "asleep."
你大腿上的是冰淇淋 对吧？
That's ice cream on your lap, correct?
的确如此
It is indeed.
赫德小姐让我拿着冰淇淋 因为她注意到我在点头
Uh, Ms. Heard asked me to hold the ice cream as she noticed that I was on a... on the nod,
意思是快睡着了
that means "falling asleep,"
我那天工作了17个小时 而且我摄入了阿片类药物
um, from the 17-hour day that I'd worked, and also the opiates that I'd ingested,
那是她拍的一张绝妙的照片
and that was a wonderful picture to take for her.
我不知道她为什么要拍
- Sure... - I don't know why she took it.
所以拍到那张照片是赫德小姐的问题
Well, so it's Ms. Heard's fault that that picture was taken.
你是这意思吗？
That's... Is that what you're saying?
是她拍的
She... She snapped it.
陪审团对这个信息的解读会很有趣
Interesting to see how the jury interpret this information.
他们会像赫德希望的那样 认为是约翰尼拥有黑暗面的证据？
Will they interpret it, as Ms. Heard wants, as evidence of Johnny having a "dark side"?
还是说他们会像约翰尼说的那样
Will they interpret it as evidence, as Johnny says,
解读成女朋友 故意让她的伴侣看起来像坏人？
of a girlfriend setting up her partner to look like a bad guy?
关注我 了解更多
Follow me for more legal TikTok.
-你拍了这张照片吗 赫德小姐？ -没错
- You took this photo, right, Ms. Heard? - That's correct.
你决定拍德普睡在地板上的照片？
So you decided to take a picture of Mr. Depp asleep on the floor?
他昏倒了
He was passed out.
你也拍了这张照片
You took this picture as well.
是的
Yes.
这是德普先生度假时 在他的热带岛屿上
This is a picture of Mr. Depp taking a nap on his tropical island, on vacation.
小憩
我们在度假 是的
We were on vacation, yes.
-你也拍了这张照片吗 赫德小姐？ -没错
- You also took this picture, right, Ms. Heard? - That's correct.
这是德普先生 睡在椅子上的另一张照片
And this is another picture of Mr. Depp asleep in a chair.
不 他在点头
No, he was, um, nodding off.
睡觉不一样
Uh, "asleep" is different.
当你在点头时 说明你嗑药嗑嗨了
When you're nodding off, you're high on drugs.
他甚至没有感觉到 拿在手上的香烟烧到了他的腿
He didn't even feel the cigarette in his hand that had, you know, been burning on his leg.
我认为这是警报 因为我非常在意他
Uh, it was cause for alarm for me, naturally, um, because I cared about him.
你似乎很喜欢 在德普先生睡觉的时候给他拍照
You seem to like taking pictures of Mr. Depp while he's sleeping, don't you?
我非常讨厌
I hated it.
你决定拍一张德普 浑身都是冰淇淋睡着的照片
You decided to take a picture of Mr. Depp asleep with ice cream spilled all over him.
这照片里的他不是很好看吧？
This isn't a very flattering picture of Mr. Depp, is it?
不好看
No, it's not.
你把这张照片发给了你的朋友 洛基佩宁顿
You did, in fact, send this picture to your friend, Rocky Pennington.
是的 我发了
Yes, I did.
这是你在保护德普先生吗？
And this is you protecting Mr. Depp?
这是我在寻求最好朋友的支持
That is me getting support from my best friend.
这是你在支持德普先生吗？
This is you supporting Mr. Depp?
这是我寻求最好朋友的支持
This is me getting support from my best friend.
我也需要支持
I also need support.
天啊 我…
- My God, I'm... - I'm so disappointed!
我对你很失望 安迪 这太让人难过了
I'm so disappointed in you, Andy.
很抱歉 各位 真相已经出来了
I'm so sorry, guys. The truth is there. It's so upsetting.
我是怪物 因为我昨晚在床上昏倒了
I'm a monster. I must be a monster because I passed out on my bed last night,
亚米拍了一张照片 然后就完了
and Yami took a photo and it's over.
你们敢相信吗 这都能被作为证据？
Can you guys friggin' believe this was put into evidence?
他在度假的时候小憩了一下 这照片是他妈什么东西？
He's taking a freaking nap on vacation! Like, what the fuck is this photo?
这里面还有钱的因素
- There is a money aspect to this too. - Yes.
社交媒体 网红
Social media, now influencers,
你们以研究这个为生
you... you study this for a living, I don't have to tell you,
他们有时候会因为发布内容而挣钱
they make money sometimes for posting content.
在这个特定的时刻 这是如何发挥作用的？
How... How is that playing into this particular moment?
今天就加入吧
Become a member today.
按下加入按钮 你就在支持本频道
Hit that join button. You'll be supporting the channel.
我们很希望得到你的点赞
We would love if you hit the like button.
这会让YouTube的算法之神眷顾我们
It does help us with the YouTube algorithm gods.
请一定要记得
You need to make sure the next thing you do,
狂按订阅按钮
no matter what, is smash the hell out of that subscribe button.
（在庭审的过程中）
（内容创作者获得了 数百万美元的收益）
YouTube一类的平台上有些创作者
You have creators on platforms like YouTube
之前发布的视频只有数百播放量
who previously were getting hundreds of views on videos about anything,
内容从电子游戏到音乐到艺术都有
ranging from video games to music to art.
突然之间 他们开始产出 与这场审判相关的视频
All of a sudden, they're pumping out videos about this trial.
我订阅了一些频道 参与直播很有趣
I'm subscribed to some of you and it's... it's cool to... to be on a stream.
让约翰尼·德普看起来很棒 让安柏·赫德看起来很糟糕的视频
Videos that make Johnny Depp look good and make Amber Heard look bad
因为人们只想看到这类视频
because a... those are the only ones that people want to see,
而这是他们有史以来第一次挣到钱
and they're being able to make money for the first time ever.
他们关于这次审判的视频大爆
They're getting viral videos off of this case,
得到数百万播放量
getting millions of views.
你们都疯了 我非常感谢你们
Y'all have gotten wild, and I appreciate you.
这就是我们要走的路
This is the road that we're on.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
看着数字上涨很有趣 我非常感激
It's kinda fun to just watch the numbers spiral, and I appreciate it.
这是一张疯狂的成长图表
This is a... This is a wild growth chart.
你一直在说： “这是美化约翰尼·德普”
You know, you keep saying, "It's glorifying Johnny Depp."
-但这就是主流意见 对吧？ -是的
- But that is the dominant stream, right? - Oh, yes.
而不是相反
It's not the other way.
直到最近
Up until recently,
你都找不到 任何支持安柏·赫德的抖音用户
you really couldn't find any TikToks in support of Amber Heard.
整个平台都支持约翰尼·德普
- Wow! - The entire platform was pro-Johnny Depp.
我听创作者们自己说 如果有人评论
And I've heard from those creators themselves that if someone comments
说他们的立场是中立的 或者他们认为安柏也许是受害者
and says that they have a neutral position or they think that maybe Amber is a victim,
他们马上就会被围攻和骚扰 在评论区里被虐待
they immediately get dog-piled, harassed, abused themselves in these comment sections,
没有人想为安柏·赫德说话
and no one wants to speak up in support of Amber Heard.
在这场备受关注的审判进行时
And as this high-profile trial plays out in court,
社交媒体用户 团结在约翰尼·德普周围
social media users are... are sort of rallying around Johnny Depp,
就像史蒂夫提到的那样
as Steve alluded to.
他们在辩方的证明中寻找漏洞
They're... They're looking for holes in the defense's case,
他们觉得找到了一个
and they think that they found one.
这是安柏在和德普交往的全过程中 都带在包里的东西
This is what Amber carried in her purse for the entire relationship with Johnny Depp.
这是她用的
This was what she used.
她已经可以熟练混合不同的颜色
She became very adept about how she had to mix the different colors
来遮盖不同程度的淤青
for the different days of the bruises to be able to cover those.
米拉尼美妆公司被牵扯进了这个案子
So Milani Cosmetics is the company that is sort of jumping into the fray in this case.
他们说他们的美妆调色盒 于2017年问世
They said that their, uh, color correcting compact, it's a compact that came out in 2017.
辩方律师说安柏·赫德
It was the same compact that, uh, defense attorneys used
正是使用的这款产品
to say that, uh, Amber Heard used this specific kit
遮盖她被约翰尼·德普打出的淤青
to cover bruises she allegedly received from Johnny Depp.
米拉尼加入争论 发布了一条抖音
Now, Milani jumped into the fray by posting a TikTok to say,
“实际上 这款产品是2017年问世的
"Actually, this kit came out in 2017."
赫德在2016年申请和德普离婚
"Amber Heard filed for divorce from Johnny Depp in 2016."
她不可能用这款产品 来遮盖她所谓的淤青”
"There's no way that she used this specific kit in order to cover alleged bruises."
（米拉尼美妆抖音 2022年）
♪ There's one thing You can expect from me ♪
（她在交往期间一直带在包里）
（米拉尼）
（确认于2017年发布）
这只是举例她用的是这类东西
This was just an example of something that she used,
不是她真正使用的产品
and this is not the actual compact that she used,
但很多人用米拉尼美妆发的抖音说
but many people took the TikTok that Milani Cosmetics posted, and said,
“嘿 这完全能证明 安柏·赫德的律师们在撒谎”
"Hey, this is definitive proof that Amber Heard's attorneys are lying."
安柏·赫德在和德普的审判中
Amber Heard just got exposed
又被戳穿了一个弥天大谎
in another big lie from her court case with Johnny Depp.
她说安柏把这个放在包里
She said that Amber carried that in her purse
在整个交往期间都用它来遮盖淤青
to cover the bruises through her entire relationship.
这个遮瑕盘直到离婚后才问世
Well, that palette didn't come out until after the divorce.
这意味着这个遮瑕盘 在他们在一起时都还不存在！
Meaning this makeup palette did not exist when they were together!
嘭！真相会让你获得自由！
Boom! And the truth will set you free!
这条抖音已经被观看过500多万次了
The TikTok has been viewed more than five million times.
好了 我现在在费尔法克斯县法院
All right, so I'm here at the Fairfax County Courthouse.
这在现实世界造成了影响
It has caused real-world consequences.
我们看到一个用户真的去往法院…
We saw one user actually go to the courthouse...
（法官办公室）
去往法官办公室
All right, going to the judges' chambers.
…找到德普的律师们说
...and seek out, uh, Johnny Depp's lawyers and attorneys,
“我有证据必须要给你们看”
and say, "I have evidence for you that you need to see."
（德普的粉丝试图亲手 送出米拉尼化妆品而受到赞扬）
（赫德案的“证据”）
有些人在批评化妆品公司
Some people are actually criticizing the cosmetics company
因为他们加入争端 说他们：“你们是为了求关注
for jumping into the fray, saying, "Hey, you did this for clout."
没必要掺和进去的”
Like, "There was no reason for you to jump in here."
（我们都在实时观看社会的倒退）
（这不是反乌托邦吧？）
（米拉尼美妆发表声明：）
（我们的视频是为了验证 我们眼尖的忠实粉丝群）
（关于庭审中提及产品的推测）
（米拉尼美妆没有）
（对该案的审判、证据 或未来结果采取正式立场）
（米拉尼美妆已经从他们的 抖音账户中删除了该视频）
我认为这里有很多人
I think a lot of people, uh, are this... as this room,
都认为“我姑且相信 安柏·赫德的指控”
which is, "I just took Amber Heard's accusations at face value."
（尼克维尔 电视嘉宾 维尔档案播客主播）
我想要相信她
I wanted to believe her.
这个化妆工具可能说明 她没有完全坦诚
Like, this makeup kit would suggest that maybe she's not completely truthful.
大家显然有倾向性 这是名人案件
People obviously have their opinions. This is a celebrity case.
德普显然在公众舆论的法庭中赢了
Johnny Depp is clearly winning right now in the court of public opinion.
安柏·赫德还是约翰尼·德普？
Amber Heard or Johnny Depp?
-你必须回答 -约翰尼·德普
- Come on, you gotta answer. - Johnny Depp.
你是相信约翰尼还是安柏？
Do you believe Johnny or do you believe Amber?
这个案子归根结底就是这样 他们不可能都是对的
And it's ultimately what this case can... comes down to. 'Cause they can't both be right.
有一个在撒谎 你相信谁？
One is lying. Who do you believe?
这大部分取决于你的倾向性
Well, that depends probably a lot on your biases.
如果你愿意相信约翰尼
And... And, uh, if you're inclined to believe Johnny,
你认可他
you just identify with him,
那么他说什么 你都会相信
then everything he says is gonna be believed,
交叉盘问中的负面消息 会被打折扣和找理由
the negative things that are brought out on cross are gonna be discounted and explained,
“也许他没有发那条信息” 嗑药的事“没有关系”
"Well, maybe he didn't send that text message." The drug stuff, "Sure, that doesn't matter."
看到了吗？我们大事化小 我们找借口 因为我们站那一边
See? We minimize, we excuse, because that's our favored party.
然后 对安柏来说
And then, for Amber, it's like,
所有关于她的负面信息
everything out there negative about her,
我们当然会抓住 因为这证明了我们的信念
it's... we seize on, "of course," 'cause that validates our belief.
我们正在看安柏·赫德 和约翰尼·德普的最后一段庭审
We are watching the final stretch of Amber Heard and Johnny Depp
以及他们在弗吉尼亚州 进行的决斗式诽谤审判
and their dueling defamation trial playing out in Virginia.
安柏·赫德 她站上了证人席
Amber Heard, she is on the stand,
在交叉盘问中努力反抗
really pushing back on the cross-examination.
你能看到一点不同
You're seeing a little bit of a... a difference
在赫德回答 卡米尔·巴斯克斯的问题时
in the way Amber Heard is answering Camille Vasquez,
卡米尔·巴斯克斯 对她的攻击性也很强
and Camille Vasquez is being extremely aggressive with her.
我们从上次暂停的地方继续看吧
Let's go back in, in the moment where we left off.
你在丹麦电视上提过 捐赠你的离婚赔偿金 是吗？
You spoke about donating your divorce settlement on a Danish TV show, correct?
我想我说过我捐给慈善机构了
Uh, I believe I said I had, um...I... I believe I said I donated it to charity.
你出现在了一个叫 《RTL深夜秀》的节目里 对吧？
You appeared on a show called RTL Late Night, right?
我不记得是哪个节目
I don't recall what it... what show it was.
请播放原告物证346号
If we could please play Plaintiff's Exhibit 346,
那是你在这个节目上出场的部分
which is a portion of your appearance on this program.
你拿到了700万的离婚赔偿金
For the divorce settlement, you got seven million dollars.
大家说都是为了钱
People were saying this is all about the money.
但后来你做了一些 扭曲整个论点的事
But then you did something that, uh, twisted that whole argument.
你怎么处理那笔钱的？
What did you do with that money?
总共700万美元 捐给…
Seven million dollars in total was donated to...
我把它分给了美国公民自由联盟 和洛杉矶儿童医院
I split it between the ACLU and Children's Hospital of Los Angeles.
美国公民自由联盟是一个人权组织
ACLU is a human rights organization?
抱歉 美国公民自由联盟 是一个非常重要的组织
Sorry, ACLU is a prominent, um, uh, organization,
美国的非营利组织
non-profit organization in the United States.
它叫美国公民自由联盟
It's called the American Civil Liberties Union,
他们为当地的边缘化社区工作
and they work on behalf of marginalized communities,
参与法律改革
uh, on the ground, in legislative reform.
你这么做非常好 因为这种事情
Right. Well, more power to you. Because that's something
-是我从来没听过的 -我什么都不想要
- I've never heard of. - I wanted nothing.
所以 在2018年10月的这场采访中
So, in this October, 2018 interview,
你说你已经把所有离婚赔偿金
you said that you had, quote, "donated," end quote,
“捐赠”给了慈善组织 是吗？
your entire divorce settlement to charity, right?
没错
That's correct.
事实上 你的原话是
And in fact, your exact words were,
“总共700万
quote, "Seven million in total."
我把它分给了美国公民自由联盟
"I split it between the ACLU
和洛杉矶儿童医院” 是吗？
and the Children's Hospital of Los Angeles," end quote.
是的 我在离婚达成和解后
- Right? - That's correct. I made that statement
就立刻做出了这个声明
as soon as I got a divorce and we reached the settlement.
我当时就认捐了
That's when I pledged it, right then.
但你当时还没有把700万赔偿金
But you hadn't donated your entitle... entire seven million dollars settlement
全部捐给慈善组织 是吧？
to charity at that point, had you?
不对
That's incorrect.
今天坐在这里 赫德小姐
Sitting here today, Ms. Heard,
你还是没有把700万美元
you still haven't donated the seven million dollars
离婚赔偿金捐给慈善组织 对吗？
divorce settlement to charity, isn't that right?
不对
Incorrect.
-我认捐了700万… -不 那不是我的问题
- I pledged the entirety... - Ms. Heard, that's not my question.
-…我打算要履行义务 -赫德小姐？
- ...I intend to fulfill those obligations. - Ms. Heard? Ms. Heard?
那不是我的问题
That's not my question.
-请试着回答 -你问的什么问题？
- Please try to answer my question. - What was your question?
今天坐在这里
Sitting here today...
你还是没有把700万美元
...you have not donated the seven million dollars,
捐赠 不是认捐 而是捐赠
"donated," not pledged, donated,
700万美元的离婚赔偿金给慈善组织
the seven million dollars divorce settlement to charity.
我用了“认捐”和“捐赠” 彼此的同义词
I use "pledge" and "donation" synonymous with one another.
-一样的 -我不觉得 赫德小姐？
- Same thing. - But I don't. Ms. Heard?
-我不认为那是同义词 -捐款就是这样的
- I don't use it synonymously. - That's how donations are paid.
赫德小姐 恕我直言
Ms. Heard, respectfully,
那不是我的问题
that's not my question.
所以 直到今天
So, as of today,
你还没有把700万美元
you have not donated seven million dollars
离婚赔偿金捐给慈善机构 是吗？
of your divorce settlement to charity, right?
我目前还没有完成那些义务
I have not been able to fulfill those p...uh, those, uh, obligations yet.
安柏真的在试图说服陪审团
Amber is literally trying to convince the jury.
她一直在看他们
And she keeps looking at the jury.
她想让陪审团相信这个故事 就是她捐赠了离婚赔偿的700万
She is trying to sell this story that she donated the whole seven million that she got from her divorce
就因为她认捐了
because she pledged it.
安柏非常善于表达
Amber is very articulate.
她非常聪明
She's very smart.
但她会看着陪审团 这在她回应问题时是很奇怪的
Um, but yes, she does look at the jury, which is a little bit weird, when she's addressing her comments.
她看陪审团的次数比这场庭审中的
She may be looking at that jury more than any other witness has
其他任何证人都要多 因为她想要获得他们的关注
in the past during this trial, because she wants to keep their attention.
那是因为你确实有所图 对吧？
And that's because you did want something, didn't you?
我什么都不想要 我也没有得到什么
I didn't want anything and I didn't get anything.
你想要德普先生的钱
You wanted Mr. Depp's money.
没拿到 没兴趣 我爱过约翰尼 这是我当初跟他在一起的原因
Didn't get it, wasn't interested in it. I loved Johnny, that's why I was with him.
你想得到正面的曝光
You wanted good press.
总的来说 谁都想要正面的曝光 是的
In general, one... ...does want good press, yes.
你想在公众面前表现出利他主义
You wanted to seem altruistic publicly.
我不感兴趣
Wasn't my interest.
我的兴趣在于我的名声 澄清我的名声
Uh, my interest is, uh, in my name, in clearing my name,
而当时我被称为骗子 我的动机被质疑
and, at the time, I was being called a liar and my motives were being questioned.
我觉得把这件事说清楚很重要
I did see it as important to... clear that up.
我想发表一个声明 以确保没有任何疑问
I wanted to make a statement, to make sure that there was n-not any doubt,
我不能因为约翰尼是更大的明星 得到更多的宣传
that I couldn't be labeled these things just because Johnny was a bigger star
就被贴上这些标签
and had more publicity reach.
你想提醒大家
You wanted to remind everyone
你对德普先生 家庭暴力的指控 是吗？
of your claims of domestic violence against Mr. Depp, right?
不 我想继续我的生活
No, I wanted to move on with my life.
你想让那些说法看起来可信
You wanted to make those claims seem believable.
-它们是可信的 它们很可信 -你想让大家看到
- They are believable. They were believable. - You wanted them to be seen...
你想被看作是 抱歉 一个高尚的家庭暴力受害者
You wanted to be seen, excuse me, as a noble victim of domestic violence, didn't you?
我从没想过被当成受害者
I have never, never wanted to be seen as a victim.
-我也没说过自己是 -你…
- Nor have I ever called myself one. - You...
你宣过誓
You testified under oath,
“你的离婚赔偿金 会被全额捐赠给慈善组织”不是吗？
that, quote, "The entirety of your divorce settlement was donated to charity," end quote. Didn't you?
没错 我认捐了全部金额
That's correct. I pledged the entirety.
（安柏·赫德的交叉盘问 导致互联网又进行了一番奚落）
赫德和她的捐款是怎么回事？
What's the big deal with Amber Heard and these donations?
“骗子屎德”又一次暴露了自己 这可能让她输掉整场审判
"Scamber Turd" exposed herself yet again and it might have just cost her the entire trial.
匹诺曹可能要告她盗窃身份 因为她撒了这么多谎
Pinocchio might have to sue her for identity theft, these lies are getting out of hand.
你捐钱直接认捐就可以了？
You pay donations through pledging them?
不 你得付钱
No, you pay...
你捐钱是把钱给他们 而不是说你会给他们
You give donations by giving them money,
not by saying you're going to give them money.
她不知道捐赠和认捐的区别
She doesn't know the difference between "donate" and "pledge."
对
Right.
我觉得我会“安柏·赫德”这件事
I think I'm gonna "Amber Heard" it, you know?
认捐1000或1200万美元给大组织
Pledge ten, twelve million dollars to a great organization.
既然认捐和捐赠是同义词
You know, and since "pledge" and "donate" is synonymous,
那事情就成了
we're all good.
（社交媒体上的一些人 迅速指出从前的例子）
（“认捐”和“捐赠” 被当做同义词使用）
（我要说多少次 美国公民自由联盟认为）
（认捐和捐赠是可以互换的词）
（安柏·赫德小姐捐款 2018付款 2018年12月11日）
（安柏·赫德小姐认捐）
（媒体/捐赠者 交替使用认捐/捐赠的例子）
（JK罗琳捐赠）
（JK罗琳认捐）
（爱莉安娜·格兰德 认捐）
（爱莉安娜·格兰德 捐赠）
（赛琳娜·戈麦斯 认捐）
（赛琳娜·戈麦斯 捐赠）
（美国公民自由联盟将130万美元 归于十年内捐赠350万美元的计划）
（洛杉矶儿童医院证实 截至2018年6月）
（他们已收到 与350万美元认捐有关的25万美元）
（他已经在舆论法庭上获胜了）
不管这个陪审团的结果是什么 他都已经赢了
He's won already in the court of opinion. Whatever this jury comes out to, he's won,
他需要法庭程序
and he needed the court process
从安柏那里取得证据和陈述
to extract evidence and statements from Amber.
这就留给我们一个真正的问题
And that leaves us to the... to... to the real question,
那就是 真正的真相是什么？
which is, what is the actual truth?
真相从哪里来？
Where does that come from?
那是陪审团的工作
That's the jury's job.
-我想知道他们是怎么选陪审团的 -我也想过
I wanna know how they picked the jury for this.
我想的是“这一定是…” 我猜想陪审团已经被隔离了
I was thinking about that too. Like, "This has gotta be..." I mean, like, I'm assuming the jury's, like, sequestered away.
-对 -这是个很大的…
- Yeah. - This is a big...
跟什么东西隔离开？
Sequestered away from where?
菲利普 你觉得社交媒体有多重要
Philip, let me start with you. How important do you think social media is, and what's going on out there
在社交媒体领域 对这个案件有什么看法？
in the social media universe, to this case?
真正重要的是 你有一个由七个人组成的陪审团
All that really matters is that you have a jury of seven
他们不会在社交媒体上发表言论 他们会纯粹根据
who does not go on social media and is going to assess what went down based purely on
法庭上提出的内容 而不是抖音或照片墙帖子
what is presented in court and not what is, you know, on TikTok or in Instagram posts
或脸书上的内容等等 来评估发生了什么
or on Facebook, etc.
（米歇尔·托马斯 辩护律师 法庭卫视音频）
他们可以跟亲朋好友互动
They've been able to interact with friends, family,
但他们不应该参与社交媒体
and so, while they're not supposed to engage in social media
不应知道公共领域发生了什么事
and know what's going on in the public sphere,
但很难说陪审团里没有人接触过
it's kind of tough to say that no one on that jury has been exposed to it whatsoever,
所以我的确认为那是个问题
so I do think that's a concern.
还有那间法庭里的人群
And the impact of the crowd cannot be overlooked
也是不能被忽视的影响因素
in that courtroom every day.
你觉得大多数情况下 陪审团都会做出正确判断吗？
Do you think that the jury gets it right in most cases?
你觉得他们了解自己的责任吗？
Do you think that they understand their responsibility?
是的 法官会告知他们应该做什么
Of course, the judge tells them what they're supposed to do.
你不能读关于这个案件的任何东西
You're not to read anything about this case.
你不能看关于这个案件的任何东西
You are not to watch anything about this case.
你不能听关于这个案件的任何东西
You're not to listen to anything about this case.
这适用于电视 报纸
This applies to television, newspapers,
杂志 网络 任何网站
magazines, the Internet, and any online sites.
更进一步说 你不能读、看或听 任何与之相关的
Further, you're not to read, watch, or listen to anything about this case
在任何社交网站上发布的内容 比如推特 脸书 照片墙
on any social networking sites such as Twitter, Facebook, Instagram,
Snapchat之类的 任何类似的网站
Snapchat, etc., or any similar sites.
陪审团应该被隔离起来 人们会希望他们不会查看任何东西
The jury should've been sequestered. You would hope that they would not look up anything.
做陪审员很难
It's very, very hard to be a juror.
我一点都不羡慕这些陪审员
I do not envy these jurors at all.
在法庭上待了六个星期
Six weeks being in that courtroom!
再说一次 不好玩
Again, it is not fun.
他们没有一个人知道 自己会参与德普案的庭审
Not one of them had a fucking clue that they were walking into Johnny Depp's fucking trial.
我觉得被转播是非常棒的
I-I-I think this is fantastic that this is being broadcasted,
而且我觉得一切都清晰起来了
and I think that everything that's coming together,
这会变得规模更大 更疯狂
this is gonna get bigger and crazier.
他刚才踢我了吗？
"Did he just kick me?"
-德普先生提请凯特·莫斯 -凯特·莫斯
Mr. Depp calls Kate Moss to the stand.
这会对安柏的证明造成不利影响
Would be a detrimental thing to Amber's case.
这是存在真正风险的
And there is a real risk
他不仅可能以原告的身份败诉
that not only could he lose this case as the plaintiff,
而且赫德还提起了一亿美元的反诉
but Heard has a $100 million counterclaim.
事情可能会很糟糕
This thing could get real bad,
对德普先生来说 甚至可能很快变得更糟
even worse, real fast for Mr. Depp.
字幕翻译：Zeo Niu